Oleh Korovai

Born: 13.07.1995 | Email: oleh.coach@gmail.com | Mobile: +47 968 62 740

Education

Educational institution Specialty

• College of Economics and Technology. Food Industry Technologist

QATestLab.
Junior QA Engineer

Ukrainian Association of Football.
Football Coaching C licence

Experiences

Cpamatica | SEO Specialist | 25.07.2022 - 10.02.2024

The main work:

- SEO audit of sites, correction of errors. Generate ideas and conduct experiments, analyze market and competitors' strategies.
- Onpage content optimization, Introduction of relinking.
- Creation technical assignment for authors, placement and design of pages, placement of links to sites.

Waypoint SEO Agency | Content Manager/SEO Assistant | 25.05.2021 - 10.07.2022

The main work:

- Filling the site with listings, articles, photos. Mark up html text and add title and description to articles projects.
- Editing html, css templates site, as well as the basic addition of JavaScript scripts.
- Creating pages and registering domains on cloudflare.

Osnova TV Company | Internet Installer/Technican | 10.12.2018 - 18.05.2021

The main work:

- Connection of subscribers to cable TV and Internet services.
- Setting up customer hardware, service and repair of Cable TV.
- Installing, configuring, and maintaining computer software.

Videographer and video editor | Hromadske TV 2017-2019 | Freelance 2018 - 2023

The main work:

Photo and video shooting. Photos and video editing. Working with light and sound.

Skills

Language Skill: Intermediate level of English, confident technical. Conversational level of Portuguese and fluency in Russian.

Tech stack: Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe After Effects, Ahrefs, Screaming Frog SEO Spider, Surferseo, ChatGPT, Google Search Console, HTML/CSS, Similarweb, excel and ms office, Sublime Text.

Summary

I can work with video filming and editing. Know how to work with html markup and css styles, I have experience with CMS WordPress, as well as with "Clean Website Code". I know and used ISPmanager web server control panel based on Linux.

I know how manually test sites and make test documentation (checklists, test-cases, test-plans, bug-reports).

My hobbies are football and fishing, i also like to shoot and edit videos.